Okay. We got to talk about Usher and the halftime show. Okay. So some of my highlights are one,
I told y'all that I thought it was going to start with, you don't have to call. I didn't get it
right, but it was the second song. Yeah. Okay. It was the second song. Yes. The first one was
caught up. I also, people were like, oh, he's not going to do any ballads. And I was like,
in what world is an R&B singer not going to go do any ballads? Now he didn't, he sang like a line.
And there was a whole lot of gyrating going on. I call it the Elvis pelvis that Usher was giving
y'all. I am always disappointed that he doesn't spell out his name. Like he does it nice and slow.
I don't know why he don't do it. Cause that was a great time for everybody. I will say he fit,
he fit in so many records and brought out JD who was dressed like a man sneaking into like,
like going back to school, pretending he's a kid like that. Not for like, not for like,
you know, menacing reasons, but just like Billy Madison of sorts. Like, I was just like, what is
this? What does this look? And then Alicia Keys came out and the piano looked amazing.
Yes. Beautiful gowns. Gowns, beautiful gowns. It was a black AF kind of show. There was roller
skates. There were stripper poles. Um, and my prediction is that next year they don't have
a country singer. Yeah, definitely. They got to, they got to.